https://www.danube-international.com/en/privacy-policy.htm

Mission and Vision
Why us?
Privacy Policy
In compliance with the regulations in force relating to personal data protection, we hereby bring the following information to your attention:
Basic information
Responsible Party
DANUBE INTERNATIONAL SARL.
Purpose
To manage the sending of information and commercial research
Additional information
Responsible Party: You are hereby informed that the party responsible for the file is the commercial company Onnera Laundry Barcelona, S.A. (henceforth, 'DANUBE'), a company with registered office at Calle Comerç, 6-12, 08504-Sant Julià de Vilatorta, Barcelona, and NIF (Tax Identification Number) A08255374.
You can contact us by calling the telephone number +33 (0)2 54 88 05 76 or by email info@danube-international.com
Purpose: The data referred to below will be gathered for the purpose of managing the sending of information and commercial research. If we do not obtain your consent, or you withdraw it in the future, we will not be able to send you commercial communications about our products.
Legitimisation: The personal data will be processed with your consent. This is the basis of the processing.
Recipients: Your personal data will not be ceded to third parties alien to the responsible party.
Similarly, international transfers of data to third parties outside of the European Union will not be carried out.
The third parties who might have access to the personal data within the framework of service provision to DANUBE, have signed the corresponding service provision contracts and ensure fulfilment of the regulations in terms of data protection.
Data categories: the personal data we will gather is the following identification data:
Name and surnames
Company
Address
Email and contact telephone number.The data gathered is necessary for the correct management of the commercial activities.
Retention period: The data will be retained for as long as the commercial relationships between yourself and DANUBE are maintained, and provided that you do not withdraw your consent.
Rights: Without prejudice to the foregoing, you have the right to request from DANUBE, access to your personal data, its rectification or deletion, to the limitation of its processing, or to oppose the processing, as well as the right to portability of your data. Moreover, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You can exercise the aforementioned rights by communicating to the email address info@danube-international.com, indicating your name and surnames, company and indicating your desire not to receive any more communications from that moment on.
If you consider that DANUBE is not complying with the regulations, you have the right to present a claim before the competent authority.
Security measures: DANUBE adopts the technical and organisational measures necessary to prevent the loss, improper use, alteration, unauthorised access or theft of the personal data provided, taking account of the state of technology, the application costs, the nature, scope, context and purpose of the processing, as well as the risks, variable in probability and severity, for your rights and freedoms.
In any case, the security measures applied by DANUBE guarantee and include:
The capacity to guarantee the permanent confidentiality, integrity, availability and resilience of the processing systems and services;
The capacity to restore the availability of and access to the personal data rapidly in the event of physical or technical incident;
A process of regular verification, evaluation and assessment of the effectiveness of the technical and organisational measures taken, to guarantee the security of the processing.
About us
Products
News
Support
Projects
Videos
Download
Contact
Legal notice
· 											Cookies policy
· 											Privacy Policy
Copyright DANUBE
We use own and third party cookies to offer our services and to collect statistical information. If you continue browsing, accept installation and use. You can change the settings or get more information on our						Cookies policy
OK
